stupeflix.com 2015-09-07

# Privacy Policy - Stupeflix

Your privacy is very important to us. We provide this privacy policy to explain our information practices and to define your options for how your information is collected and used.

## What information do we collect?

We collect personal information from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address and company name. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

We may also store non-personal information from our users, such as the purchases you may have made from us, the content you may have uploaded or created, or your account preferences.

We may also collect non-personal, technical information from our users via our web server logs, such as your Internet Protocol address, the kind of browser or computer you use, the date and time of your visit, the country or location from which you access the site, the web pages you view on our site, the web pages you go from our site or the web pages from which you link to our site. None of this information can identify you personally.

Stupeflix does not store your credit card information. Stupeflix uses outside third party payment processing companies, Paypal and Stripe, to bill you for your purchases, which may in some instances include the storage of your personal information by the third party, such as your credit card number. Paypal and Stripe have separate and independent privacy policies.

## What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience   
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website   
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service   
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions   
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails   
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.   
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information). We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their Stupeflix account and going to the 'Your Account' page available at [https://studio.stupeflix.com/me/](https://studio.stupeflix.com/me/%%7D).

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <https://studio.stupeflix.com/en/legal/terms/>

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on February 1st, 2013

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

By email:   

By mail:   
Stupeflix SAS   
c/o Privacy Manager   
49 rue Boursault   
75017 Paris   
FRANCE
